<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Kai Tebay</title>
    <link>https://kaitebay.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kai Tebay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 17:45:42 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kaitebay.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Smells Like Logical Error</title>
      <link>https://kaitebay.github.io/posts/smells-like-logical-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 17:45:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaitebay.github.io/posts/smells-like-logical-error/</guid>
      <description>As Jonah and Henry discuss on their great new episode of Techlore Talks, the &amp;ldquo;nirvana fallacy&amp;rdquo; can be detrimental to productive discussion and meaningful progress. Simply put, it&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s called an &amp;ldquo;informal fallacy&amp;rdquo;—or form of logical error—and might also be described as &amp;ldquo;all-or-nothing thinking&amp;rdquo;: if something isn&amp;rsquo;t perfect, then it&amp;rsquo;s not valuable.
Who am I, why am I writing about errors, and should you listen to me? Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Kai! I&amp;rsquo;m writing about this particular error because I was inspired by the Techlore Talks episode that I mentioned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Projects</title>
      <link>https://kaitebay.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:04:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaitebay.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>This page is a &amp;ldquo;living&amp;rdquo; list of my projects. You can use the table of contents to navigate to different projects.
Privacy Guides Privacy Guides is an open source project which provides up-to-date, evidence-based information that helps you protect yourself online.
I&amp;rsquo;m a member of the Privacy Guides team.
Generally, I aim to
 review cutting-edge research, to maintain awareness of emerging technologies and best-practices; review written content, to ensure the professional tone that Privacy Guides readers expect; contribute ideas and technical input to internal discussions; and, most importantly, advocate for digital freedoms!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Use a Kindle Without an Amazon Account</title>
      <link>https://kaitebay.github.io/posts/kindle-without-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 23:31:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaitebay.github.io/posts/kindle-without-account/</guid>
      <description>I read quite a lot—from research papers to books and articles—and, while I love the old-school combo of a book and a hot drink, found myself looking for an eReader. For me, there are two main benefits: saving space when I travel, and avoiding distractions when I read. Although there are alternatives like Kobo eReaders or the reMarkable tablet, among others, the Amazon Kindle was my first choice.
 Depending on your threat model, you might prefer to avoid interacting with Amazon’s ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://kaitebay.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaitebay.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about education, human rights, and technology. This is a website where you can find my ideas, projects, contact details, and digital presence.
 📑 Articles 🏛️ Research 🌐 Projects  Contact Keys: PGP | SSH | (Fingerprint)
 📧 Email is the best way to contact me directly.  Social media:
 💼 LinkedIn 🗨️ Mastodon 💻 GitHub  and find me on the Privacy Guides forums.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
